《实习医生格蕾》前情提要
Previously  on "Grey's Anatomy"...
那天晚上很糟  我哭得像个小姑娘
I had a bad night and I cried like a girl.
但我已经走出来了  你也需要走出去
I'm over it. You need to get over it, too.
我在重考实习测试
I'm retaking my intern test.
你和我不止是室友关系
You and I are more than just roommates.
是的  我们是朋友  现在你可能是
Yeah, we're friends. I mean, right now, you're probably
-我最好的朋友之一了  -最好的朋友
- one of my best friends.  - Best friends.
我只吻过你一个女人
You're the only woman I've ever kissed.
所以你也很害怕
So you're freaking out, too?
害怕长期的心理治疗
A lot of therapy time.
德里克搬进来了  我们之间更进了一步
Well, Derek's moved in. And we've taken it to the next level.
我很高兴
I am happy.
公元前6500年
In 6500 B.C.,
某人看着他生病的朋友说
some guy looked at his sick friend and said,
我有个办法  让我在你脑袋上凿个洞吧
"I have an idea. Why don't I drill a hole in your skull?
这样你会好受些
It'll make you feel better."
从此  外科手术诞生了
And thus, surgery was born.
梅丽去哪了
Uh, where's Mer?
她不在这儿
She's not here.
就你一个人在房间里?
So you're just in there by yourself?
我没有...  我在等她
I'm not...  I'm...I'm waiting for her.
裤子不错
Oh. Love the outfit.
-你有事吗  -我需要现金
- What do you want? - I need cash.
我叫了披萨  阿历克斯欠我20块
I ordered a pizza, and Alex owes me 20 bucks,
但是他现在不理我  就因为我看到他
but he's not speaking to me because I saw him crying
为了他的疯子女友在哭
over his crazy girlfriend.
一周前  有那么一瞬间
And there was a minute a week ago
我觉得他快要变回正常人了
that I actually thought he was gonna be a human being,
但他现在就是不肯开门
And now he won't open the door.
进浴室去  进去  快
Run into the bathroom. Just go. Go!
克莱夫
Karev.
给我20块钱
Give me a $20.
太棒了  真有你的
That was so awesome. You're pretty cool.
我不是说我以前觉得你不棒
Not that I didn't think you were cool before,
你知道的  我以前只是
But, you know, I did not.
觉得你头发超多
I kinda just thought you were all hair and, you know. Ah.
很好  你要分一点披萨吗
Now, cool. You want to share some pizza?
能想到在脑袋上打孔这样的主意
It takes a certain brand of crazy
是需要点疯狂的神经的
to come up with an idea like drilling into somebody's skull.
但医生们总是很有自信
But surgeons have always been a confident bunch.
你的衣服放进你自己的房间
Unh-Unh-Unh. Your clothes, your room.
我可不要客厅像以前那样
The living room will not be a dumping ground
变成垃圾场
like the old place was.
你没听见她说的话吗
Did you not hear her?
她有点吓到我了
Okay. She kinda scares me.
因为她本来就很吓人
'Cause she's scary.
凯丽需要新的密友
Callie needs a new best friend.
还不错  是吧
Not bad, right?
很不错
It's great.
通常我们知道自己在做什么
We usually know what we're doing,
就算不知道  也装作知道的样子
And when we don't, we still act like we do.
我们贸然进入未知的国度
We walk boldly into undiscovered country,
插上自己的旗帜  然后开始发号施令
Plant a flag and start ordering people around.
你想跟我约会吗
Do you want to go on a date with me?
那样很爽很可怕
It's invigorating and terrifying.
你是说"约会"
Like a "date" date?
是的  烛光晚餐  还有红酒
Yeah, you know, a restaurant candlelight, bottle of wine--
到了晚上我会想法子脱下你的衣服
At the end of the night, I try to take your clothes off?
好  那就...约会吧
Ooh. Okay, that's... that would be a date.
你在...
Hey. You're...
光着身子等你回来
Naked and waiting for you.
你还写日记
You keep a diary?
怎么我一直都不知道
Have I not known that all this time,
-你在写日记  -不是的  我没有
- that you keep a diary? - No, I-I-I don't.
我
I, uh--
别害羞  我觉得你这样挺可爱的
Aw, don't be shy. I think it's cute.
不是我的日记
It's not mine.
我又不会看的  是谁的日记
I won't read it. Whose is it?
你母亲的
Your mother's.
在一个大箱子里找到的
It was in a big box full of old issues
箱子里全是以前的《新英格兰医学期刊》
of "The New England Journal of Medicine."
你看过了?
Did you read it?
没有
No.
我拿出来给你的
I brought it up here for you.
你为什么翻她的东西
Why were you going through her things?
我想找个地儿放衣服
I was trying to find space for my clothes.
你的衣橱塞满了
Your closet is full.
我要洗澡了
I have to, um, shower.
今天一直在帮克里斯蒂娜搬箱子
I've been hauling Cristina's boxes.
你一个字都没看过
You haven't read any of it?
没有  要是写到我了怎么办
No, what if I'm in it?
我不想知道她是怎么看待我的
I don't want to hear what she thought of me.
我听的够多的了
I've heard enough of that already.
你觉得哪个更糟  写到你还是不写到你
What's worse, if you're in it or you're not in it?
不知道  你说他为什么
I don't know. But I mean, see, why is he in the study
突然在衣橱里
rooting around in closets...
翻我母亲的遗物呢
trying to dig up my mother's ghost?
我想是因为你让他翻的
I think 'cause you invited him.
很显然  某些人认为我上周
Apparently some people thought I was kidding last week
关于禁止医生只关注于自己喜欢的
when I announced that nobody was going to get to hang out
病例的规定是句玩笑话
on their favorite specialty anymore.
我没开玩笑  年轻医生们  别太专攻了
I wasn't. Junior residents don't specialize.
所以别再要求把你们送回到
So all the requests to send you back
你们"真正热爱"的科室了
to that place where your true heart lives can end now.
所有人听贝利医生的安排
Dr. Bailey makes the assignments.
不准跟她争执  我再说一遍  不准
Do not, and I repeat, do not harangue her.
听着  欧麦利  我打过电话了
Look, O'malley, I made a call.
分数还没出来  我知道了会告诉你的
They don't have your score yet. If I knew, I would tell you.
你肯定通过了
You passed.
今晚我们去Joe's  我们来庆祝一下
We're gonna go to Joe's tonight and we're gonna celebrate.
我请客你的啤酒和花生  随你吃多少
I'm gonna buy you a beer and all the peanuts you can eat.
-如果我没有通过呢  -我还是请你喝啤酒
- What if I didn't pass?  - Well, then I'm still buying you a beer.
为挂科请客
Beer for losers.
格蕾  你跟着汉娜去心脏科
Grey, you're on cardio with Hahn today.
-可是  -斯蒂文斯和克莱夫去缝合伤口
- Oh, but...  - Stevens and Karev, pit.
拜托
Oh, come on.
不能这样  主任让我们变动位置
That's not... The chief wants us to have a change.
这样根本没变
That's not a change.
我总是跟阿历克斯一起缝合伤口
I'm always stuck in the pit with Alex.
主任说不准跟贝利医生争
When the chief said don't harangue Dr. Bailey,
你听不懂吗?  杨  你去门诊
What do you think he meant? Yang, clinic.
-什么  不  -不  等一下
- What? What? No. - No. No, no, wait, wait.
-门诊是我的  该由我来定  -是的
- The clinic is mine. I say how it's staffed. - Yeah, yeah.
-她只会毁了那儿  -是  我会毁了那儿的
- She'll just ruin it. - Yeah, I will. I'll-I'll ruin it.
-让我去吧  -不行  你照我说的做
- Just let me do it. - No, you will not. You will do what I say.
既然杨一整天都不愿意
And since Yang couldn't be bothered to show up
去门诊室报到一下
at the clinic since it opened,
就把这当成是她新的培训方向
Think of it as a new frontier in her training.
-抱歉  -天哪  你根本不觉得抱歉
- Sorry. - Oh, oh, oh, my god. You're totally not sorry.
你走运了  居然能跟着汉娜  太走运了
You're psyched. You got Hahn. If you're not, you should be.
她人很可怕的  而你又提高了她对
Well, she's terrifying. And you have given her
住院医生知识水平的要求
unrealistic expectations as to what a resident should know.
不要谈论病情以外的东西
Just stay on top of the material, and don't get
也不要跟病人太亲近  她不喜欢这样
all warm and fuzzy with the patients. She hates that.
好的
Okay.
如果你还有问题  就来问我
If you have any questions, just come and ask me.
我会一直呆在门诊室里给衰人们绑绷带
I'll be in the clinic putting band-aids on stupid whiners
那些不善于受伤的家伙
who don't have the balls to get real injuries.
1号到4号  跟我走
One through four, let's go. Come on.
我没有看过那本日记
I didn't read the diary.
我碰巧找到了  拿出来放在桌子上而已
I just found it and put it on the table.
我是你的话我会看的
I would've read it.
每次我想要搬进她家
Every time I actually do something
她总是很焦虑不安
to move into the house, she freaks out.
你打算怎么处理那辆车
What are you gonna do with the trailer?
不处理
No.
为什么不
Come on.
她很可能会在一周内赶我出去
This is a very real possibility she kickes me out in a week.
我不能没有那辆车
I'm not letting go of the trailer..
伤口  粪便阻塞  一堆伤口
Sutures, fecal impaction and more sutures.
-交给她了  -你什么意思  交给我做
- She'll do it. - What do you mean, she'll do it?
你对这些无聊透顶的事情很熟悉
You're good at boring, stupid crap.
你就是个专家
You're like a specialist.
你好  我是斯蒂文斯医生
Hi, I'm Dr. Stevens.
看来你需要缝几针  发生了什么事
Looks like you need some stitches. What happened?
我划伤了
I have a cut.
怎么伤的
How'd you get it?
我把遥控器扔他头上了  没什么大不了的
I threw a remote at him, okay? It's no big secret.
他除了看电视什么事都不做
I threw it at him because all he can do is watch television
-要么睡得像个死人一样  -亲爱的
- or fall asleep like a dead person. - Honey
别叫我亲爱的  我要跟你离婚
Don't "honey" me. I'm divorcing you.
等你的伤口止血之后
As soon as you stop bleeding from your head,
我们就去找律师
We're going to a lawyer.
你去过欧洲吗
You ever been to Europe?
-没  打算以后去  -别等到退休了才去
- Nope. Someday. - Don't wait until you're retired
到时候你都不想看看窗外的景色了
And you can't be bothered to look out the window.
6个月的环球旅行
6-month trip across the world...
我等了15年了
I've been waiting for it for 15 years...
-他却整天就是睡觉  -Marianne
- He slept through the whole thing. - Marianne...
睡遍了六大洲
Six continents.
我工作了30年  我真的很累
I worked for 30 years. I was very tired.
我也很累
Well, I'm tired, too,
嫁给这个对世界毫无兴趣的男人
of being married to somebody with no interest in the world,
大家都很累  我要去买点咖啡
So everybody's tired. I'm gonna go get some coffee.
-我想应该是一去不回了  -也许吧
- I assume this is going to take forever. - Probably.
你的嘴总是这样朝旁边动吗
Does your mouth always do that, move to the side like that?
怎么个动法
Like what? Huh.
介意我给你做些测试吗
Mind if I run some tests?
-你决定吧  -很好
- Whatever you want. - Great.
也许我是错的  但我觉得戈兰蒂先生
I may be wrong about this, but I think Mr. Grandy
神经系统有问题
has a major neuro thing going on.
-把他缝好后做个断层扫描  -好的
- So get him stitched up and then get him up for a C.T., okay? - Okay.
这个给我
Oh, give me that.
给我
Give it.
戈兰蒂先生  我是克莱夫医生
Mr. Grandy, uh, I'm Dr. Karev,
我将为你做断层扫描
and I will be taking you up for your C.T. today.
邓肯 佩利  8岁  最近诊断为
Duncan Paley, age 8, recently diagnosed
感染性心内膜炎引起的主动脉瓣疾病
with aortic valve disease from an infectious endocarditis.
他预定今天做自体动脉瓣置换术
He's scheduled for a ross procedure today.
-他的儿科医生嘱咐说...  -邓肯
- There's a note from his pediatrician...  - Duncan!
-邓肯 回来  -邓肯
- Duncan, get back here. - Duncan!
拦住他  抓住他
Stop him. Grab him.
还不快去
Go.
抱歉
Sorry.
邓肯
Duncan.
邓肯  回来
Duncan. Duncan, come back here.
邓肯  你快点下来  从椅子上下来
Duncan, you get down from there right now. Duncan, get off the chair.
别  别碰火警的警铃
No, do not. Don't touch the fire alarm.
我不做手术
I'm not having surgery.
别拉那玩意儿  那样很不好
Do not pull that. That would be very, very bad.
-乖孩子  -不
- Munchkin...  - No!
快点  孩子  下来
Come on, kiddo, get down.
-我不做手术  -1  2...
- I'm not doing it. - One, two...
-不做手术  -3
- No!  - Three.
倒数对他没用
Counting doesn't work.
-我觉得不会有事的  只要...  -你要保证不做手术
I think this is all gonna be okay if we just-- Promise me no surgery.
保证不会给我做手术
Promise me no surgery.
我...  我们...
O--I--We--
我们没办法保证
We can't really do that.
所有人撤离  所有人撤离
Evacuate. Evacuate.
所有人撤离
Evacuate.
紧急事件
This is an emergency.
所有人撤离
Evacuate.
我们能管住这孩子了吗
Do we have this kid under control,
还是需要我打电话给社会服务机构
or do I have to call social services?
他不会再做这样的事了
He won't do anything like that again.
最好是这样  上周该死的天花板漏水
He'd better not. The damn ceiling fell last week.
我不想再来一系列假警报
I don't need a series of false alarms.
这里看上去已经够傻帽的了
This place looks ridiculous enough already.
把那小子看牢点儿
Keep the ankle biter under control.
如果必要的话  我会给他注射镇定剂的
I'll sedate him if I have to.
很好  认真准备你的自体肺移植术
Good, and bone up on your pulmonary autografts.
我可不想整天被你的无知
I don't want to spend the day bathed in your ignorance
和无能而束缚
as well as your incompetence.
她恨死我了
Oh, she hates me.
你什么意思  必要时注射镇静剂
What do you mean, we'll sedate him if we have to?
我只是不想表现得跟病人太亲近
I was just trying not to be warm and fuzzy.
我不会给他注射的  我只是看住他而已
I don't mean sedate him, I just mean babysit him.
今天是你最后一天实习日了
It's your last day as an intern.
你多想想以后的开心日子吧
Just think of how happy you'll be to move on.
7点前我都在手术室里
I'm gonna be in the O.R. till 7:00.
八点吃晚饭不晚吧?
Is 8:00 too late for dinner?
不  但是如果你想改天或者取消的话...
No, but if you need to reschedule or cancel--
拜托  你搞笑啊?
Come on. Are you kidding?
我已经在canto定了位子了
I made a reservation at canto.
穿什么衣服我都想好了
I even gamed out an outfit.
我们要去约会
We are doing this.
汉娜在做一个换膜手术
So Hahn is doing a ross procedure,
而且她还觉得我是个白痴
And she thinks I'm a moron. Well,
首先  那叫做自体动脉瓣置换术
First of all, it's called a pulmonary autograft
她喜欢听专业词  告诉她你很高兴
She likes the technical names. Okay, tell her you're excited
能观看她获取肺动脉瓣
To watch her harvest the pulmonary valve
用的是她的间隔分离术
Using her septal-sparing technique.
如果你切过多的隔膜肌肉
If you cut too much of the septal muscle,
-病人就需要靠呼吸机活了 -这些书本里都没有
The patient won't be able to come off pump. None of that is in the book.
这是这个手术的要诀  这样至少让她觉得
It's the key to the case. It'll make you sound like
-你至少还略知一二  -太好了
You've been around the block once or twice. Perfect.
我都不敢相信我会告诉你这些诀窍
I can't believe I am giving you all my best stuff
-你根本不配知道  -杨医生
You totally don't deserve it. Uh, dr. Yang.
Mrs. Borsokowski需要你去看看
Mrs. Borsokowski needs your loving attention.
发红  发痒  发炎  是皮疹啊
Redness, itching, inflammation--a rash.
你给我个皮疹病人?
You're giving me a rash?
不  她太刻薄了  我不要她
No, she's the mean one. I don't want her.
好吧
O-okay.
好吧  什么情况
All right. What do we got?
你看  这东西比一个棒球还大
Take a look. The thing's bigger than a baseball.
就在眼球后面
It's right behind his eyes.
有意思  呼叫斯蒂文斯
This should be fun. Page Stevens.
她把这个人交给我了
She left the guy with me.
她把这病例交给你了?
She gave you the case?
没错  伊兹觉得对不起我
Yeah, well, Izzie felt bad for me.
你知道  这样能让我开心起来
You know, figured this would cheer me up.
那样的话  我把那个东西取出来的时候你就应该来帮我
In that case, you're gonna help me pull this thing out.
邓肯
Hey, Duncan.
我们要在你手臂上做一个静脉注射  不会太久
We're gonna put an i.V. in your arm real quick,
-然后你就能继续玩了  好吗?  -做什么?
And then you can go back to your playing, okay? What is it?
-就是插一支小管子在你手臂上  -不要
Oh, it's a little tube we put in your arm. No.
-邓肯 -不要  会痛的
Duncan-- no, it's gonna hurt.
-孩子  不会痛的  -是  是会疼的
Come on, kiddo. It's not gonna hurt. No, it's gonna hurt.
因为有针头  必然会疼
It's a needle. It's gonna hurt.
但只有大概持续  3秒钟?
But it's only for, what, three seconds?
我不信你
I don't believe you.
你不相信我?
You don't believe me?
你要我证明给你看吗?
Do you want me to prove it to you?
我来证明  让格蕾医生帮我弄下
I'll prove it. I'll have dr. Grey put one in me.
这是止血带
This is a tourniquet,
把它缠在你手臂上
And, uh, you wrap it around your arm
这样你的静脉就显出来了
So that your vein pops out.
看到了?就像这个?
See? Like that?
那么现在就针刺了
So now the needle--
这就会有点痛了
That's the part that's gonna hurt.
扎进去
That goes in,
这就是  没错
And that's--yeah.
痛  有点痛
Hurting. That hurts.
会痛  但是...
It hurts and...
马上就不痛了
It doesn't hurt any more.
然后血流到这里
And now that stuff goes into here.
一点都不痛
Doesn't hurt at all.
好吧  我做
Okay, I'll do it.
好的  那我去再拿套注射器
Okay. Then I'll go get another i.V. Kit.
好的
Okay. Okay.
你很在行
You're really good at this.
我在他这个年纪的时候也喜欢玩飞机
Oh, I was an airplane guy, too, when I was his age.
我们这种飞友
Us airplane guys,
比较好奇事物的原理
I think we just like to know how things work.
我很抱歉弄了火警
I'm sorry about the alarm.
我知道
I know.
动起来!
Move!
他们居然还有脸去发火
They have the nerve to be indignant
就因为新规定不允许
About how they're not allowed
他们只重视专科
To be on their specialties anymore.
他们现在不能只攻专科
They don't have specialties.
但是他们应该感激他们还能参加别的...
They should be grateful they're even allowed in the--
你在听我说么?
Are you listening to me?
我要和爱瑞克·汉娜约会了
I'm going on a date with Erica Hahn.
这太奇怪了
And, uh, that's awkward
因为...
'cause, uh...
我们是同事  因为她是主治医师
She's a colleague and because she's an attending
还因为她是个女人
And because she's a she.
虽然我们有过接吻
And, uh, there's been kissing,
但没有身体接触
But, uh, no touching.
要是我不想这样下去怎么办?
And what if I'm not into it?
要是我很糟怎么办?
What if I'm horrible
我是说  那个很难
At all that's tough... South...
'国境以南 太阳以西'
Of the border?
我还从来没有越过那个国境
'cause I've never been south of the border
和一个女的干过
With a female.
我是说  我甚至都没和女人
I mean, i--i've never even been over the, uh,
有过亲密接触  你明白我说的意思吧
Northern mountains, you know what I'm saying?
当我没说过
We're gonna pretend this didn't happen.
戈兰蒂先生  你在这里干什么
Mr. Grandy? What are you doing in here?
他们让我进来的
They admitted me.
我的新医生  克莱夫医生
My new doctor, dr. Karev,
他说我脑袋里有个大肿瘤
Said I have a huge tumor in my head.
你看到我妻子了么
Have you seen my wife?
你的新医生?
Your new doctor?
有人呼我?
Somebody paged me?
我这儿有个触痛性红斑病人
Oh, I have a patient with tenderness and erythema
从上胸一直到左臂都有
Extending from her upper chest to her left arm.
我认为她该接受冲洗和清创术治疗
I'm thinking she needs irrigation and debridement.
她说你会切除我的手臂
She said you may have to amputate my arm.
不会的  只是个简单的皮疹
No. That's a simple rash.
-可能只是皮炎  -不是的  你看脱皮了
It's probably dermatitis. No, no, no, but look how the skin is denuded.
不是什么食肉菌
(以前有个病人得食肉菌 杨总想截肢)
可能会手术  对吧  是有可能的
It could be surgical, right? It's possible-- it's
只是个皮疹  如果干燥了就保湿  反之亦然
A rash. If it's dry, wet it. If it's wet, dry it
去皮肤科  拿点护肤霜
Go to derm, get a tube of cerave cream,
别再试图呼我做手术了
And don't ever page me to hustle a surgery again.
昨天就应该修好的
It was supposed to be done yesterday, done.
那么为什么我走进手术室
So exactly why did I walk into my O.R.
还是一团糟  还是一个洞
And still see a massive, gaping hole
依然在天花板该出现的位置
In where the ceiling was supposed to be?
如果看到克莱夫  拿个18号针
If you see Karev, get an 18-gauge needle
-插进他的喉咙  -我优雅的表情
And shove it in his throat. I have cultivated a look
已经告诉你们  我不关心你们的私事
That says I'm not interested in your personal problems.
你们这些白痴不懂察言观色吗
Can you morons not read that look,
还是以为我说着玩的  因为我今天一直在聆听
Or have I lost the hang of it? Because people are telling me
你们的个人问题
A lot of personal problems today.
我不管你们的超负荷工作
I don't give a crap about your crushing workload
还是你们莫名其妙的感情生活或是腕管综合症
Or your baffling love life or your carpal tunnel syndrome.
我只关心卡鲁西女士
All I care about is mrs. Carrucci,
一个92岁老人  在需要时却找不到人
A 92-year-old woman who no one can seem to find.
我是佩曼医生  有什么需要
I'm dr. Pepman. Can I help you?
护肤霜在哪里拿?
Where can I get some cerave cream?
我们的护士好像很忙
Our nurses look like they're tied up,
但如果你不急  我可以帮你去拿
But if you don't mind waiting, I can get it for you myself.
在你等的时候要来点树莓果汁喝吗?
Would you like some water with raspberries while you wait?
好啊
yeah, sure.
克里斯
Chris.
别介意克里斯
don't mind Chris.
他是我的按摩治疗师
He's our massage therapist.
你的...什么?
Your... Uh, what?
我们的手都是做精细活的
Our Hands do such delicate work,
保持健康很重要
It's important that they stay healthy.
所以我们请来克里斯帮忙按摩下
So we have Chris on staff to work on us
在我们有空的时候
When we have a spare moment.
每个主治医师都有人按摩?
Every attending gets their Hands massaged at work?
不是的
no.
皮肤科的主治医师有其他的治疗师
The dermatology attendings have another therapist.
克里斯只是帮住院医生
Chris just works on the residents.
你是住院医生?
You're a resent?
第一年
First year,
我很喜欢
And loving it.
我在两耳之间做一个切口
So I'll make an incision ear to ear
-之后剥离面部  -然后我打开前额
Then peel down the face. And I'll crack open his forehead,
把肿瘤取出来
Pull the tumour right out.
离视神经非常接近
Close to his optic nerve.
手抖一下  他就瞎了
Somebody twitches, and this guy's blind.
-你的哪个室友将协助你?  -克莱夫
Which one of your roommates will be assisting? Karev.
很好
great.
谢博特医生  我想要回来参加这个手术
Dr. Shepherd, I want back on this case. Mm-hmm.
他是我的病人  阿历克斯从我这里偷去的
This is my patient. Alex stole him from me.
斯蒂文斯还记得我跟你说过么...重申一遍
Remember when I was telling you that-- dr. Stevens, let's be clear.
在这医院  我不是你的室友
In this hospital, I am not your roommate.
我不管你的个人问题
I don't give a crap about your personal problems.
我有一个住院医生了已经够了  -谢博特医生
I have a resident. I don't need another one. Dr. Shepherd.
什么?  病人在病房里了
Yes? Patient's in his room
-你是否想跟他介绍下手术过程  -很好
If you want to go over the procedure with him. Great.
你这狗娘养的
You son of a bitch.
找个关心你的人哭去吧
Go cry to somebody who cares.
这是我的病例  这不公平
This is my case. It isn't fair.
外科就像在狂野的西部
Surgery's like the wild West.
你不是去银行声明占领某地
You didn't get your claim in montana from the bank.
明白不  你得把地圈起来
You got it 'cause you put a fence around it
谁靠近就射死他
And shot the ass off anyone who walked by.
克莱夫是个牛仔  你不是
Karev's a cowboy. You're not.
我们要切断大动脉
We're gonna transect the great arteries
在窦管的边缘
At the sinotubular ridge,
用自体移植物代替主动脉根
Use the autograft to replace the aortic root,
然后再缚上取自肺部的自体移植物
And then attach a pulmonary homograft.
你是否打算用间隔分离技术
Are you going to use the septal-sparing technique
-在取肺自体移植物上?  -对  有问题么
For the pulmonary autograft? Yes, why do you ask?
有  因为如果我们切得太多的隔膜肌肉
Well, because if we cut too much of the septal muscle,
那么病人就离不开呼吸机  对吧
We won't be able to take the patient off pump, right?
对
Right.
太好了  我一直希望看次间隔分离技术
Great. I've always wanted to see a septal-sparing technique.
你知道怎么把冠状动脉
Do you know how to reanastomose the coronary arteries
-接回大动脉吗  -知道
Back on to the aorta? I do.
那好  我让你进手术室观摩的
Well, I'll let you sew part of it in.
记得来  可能会用到你
Gonna be in there. Might as well get your Hands dirty.
好  谢谢  汉娜医生
Great. Thanks, dr. Hahn.
你这个骗子要下地狱
You're going to hell 'cause you're a liar.
刚才有破绽吗?
Was it obvious?
不幸的是  没有
Unfortunately, no.
怎么了
What?
-发生什么了  -快看
What happened? Look.
你说有急事
You paged me 9-1-1.
我正研究自体动脉瓣置换术  汉娜要做这个
I'm in the middle of studying for Hahn's pulmonary autograft,
-我没看到有什么紧急情况  -不  不  不
And I don't see an emergency. No, no, no.
他们是住院医生
They're residents.
那个  烤了一个7层蛋糕
That one... Baked a 7-layer cake
因为那边那个生日  从和面开始
For that one's birthday, from scratch.
那个...那个的女朋友
Oh,and that one, that one's, uh, girlfriend...
周末要带他去滑雪
Is taking him skiing this weekend.
但这个最彪悍
Oh, but this one's the best.
没错  这个马上早退做面膜去
Okay, this one gets to leave to go get a facial.
她还告诉了她的主治医师  主治医师还很高兴
And she told her attending, and her attending was happy
因为她们得做面膜
'cause they have to have facials.
她们是皮肤科医生
They're dermatologists.
我是说  我的神啊
I mean... Oh, my god.
医院还专门请了人给他们做按摩
The hospital has hired someone to rub them...
全天服务
Full-time.
我赌她们的男友肯定不会乱翻
I bet their boyfriends don't go digging around
-她们的衣柜连问都不问一下  -绝对不会
In their closets without asking. Never.
我告诉汉娜医生我知道
Ooh. I told Hahn I knew how to do
怎么做做冠状动脉结合手术
A coronary artery reanastomosis.
你不知道
You don't.
没错  我查了下书  但那孩子才8岁
I know. I looked it up, but the kid's 8.
-他的动脉太小了  -好的  这样吧
He's got tiny little arteries. Okay, you know what?
你去那边给我抢点葡萄过来
Um, snag me some of those grapes there,
我就教你
And I'll teach you.
再去找戴西佩曼医生
Oh, and then find dr. Daisy Pepman.
-拿一个缝合包和7-0聚丙烯  -戴西佩曼医生?
Ask her for a suture kit and a 7-0 polypropylene. Dr. Daisy Pepman?
她是个住院医生  还会给你倒果汁
She's a resident. She pours fruity drinks.
因为她有时间做这些事
'cause she has time for that kind of thing.
我喜欢呼唤她的名字
And I like saying her name.
那么是带连字符的(无礼用语)  还是她父母
So is that hyphenated, or did her parents
-给她取的名  戴西  -不  别嘲
Name her Daisy-- no, no. Hey, no--no mocking
皮肤科这不准嘲笑
There is no mocking in derm...
只有温暖和光明
only warmth and light.
您还好吗  佩瑞夫人
You all right  Mrs  Paley?
你想去看邓肯在干什么吗
You want to know what duncan's doing?
他正在打包走人
Packing to leave
我不能劝服他
And I can't stop him
我嘴都说干了
I suck at this
我累了也乏了
I'm tired and I'm fried
我晚上醒来听见他在说梦话
Because I lie awake at night listening to him breathe
我怕他心脏停止跳动
because I'm afraid his heart's gonna stop and
也许只有他死了  我才能睡着
And he's gonna die  and I'll have been sleeping
我不知道如何是好
I don't know how to do this
没人知道
Well  no one knows
怎么去做好一个得了心脏病的小孩的妈妈
How to be the mom of a kid with heart failure
没人教这个
Nobody teaches that
但是你有一个实在的聪明的小孩  你知道怎么做
And you have a really smart kid  You know that
我们只需要让游戏有趣一点  让我试试
We just need to up our game a little bit  Can I try?
试试吧
Oh  go for it
-一个棒球?  -这就是你嗜睡的原因
-A base ball? -Which is why you were so lethargic.
所以我就把我们的旅途都睡掉了?
Why slept through most of our trip breath？
不是因为我这个人很乏味 对这个精彩的世界无动于衷?
Not because I am boring,not interested in cultures of the world.
我真的不知道这件事
How was I supposed to know?
你应该体谅我  而不是朝我扔遥控器
You were supposed to give me the benefit of the doubt,not throw electronics at me.
戈兰蒂女士  这是一个良性的肿瘤
Mrs Grandy, this is a massive tumour
那个区域很难触及到  我们得跟你妻子谈谈这个
And the area is hard to reach.And we want to talk about this to your wife.
我想她很乐意去做善后的事情
Oh I am sure she is fine with the rest.
-亲爱的  -我会继续把没睡玩的地方睡玩的
-Honey -I'm going through it, then nothing left lose.
手术室见
See you in the OR.
谢博德医生 那是我的病人 我敢肯定你有权指使住院医师
Dr. Shepherd,that is my patient.,that is my patient.I'm sure you can use the resident even if you cannot.
斯蒂文斯  我可不是游戏场上的裁判
Stevens,I am not the traffic cop on the playground.
这不是游戏场  是西部荒野区!
No,it's not the playground. It's the wild,wild west.
-你能做下司法长官吗?  -在切开他的前额时我会考虑你的
Can't you be the sheriff? I'll think of you when we crack his forehead open
我不会让你这么对我的  阿历克斯
I'm not letting you do this to me  Alex
有种别走开  克莱夫
Do not walk away from me  Karev
把我的手术还给我  不然我把你的屁股打烂
Give me back my surgery or I'll shoot your ass off!
他抢了一个很大的手术
He stole a very big surgery
我会把它抢回来的
I'll pick it up
你把日记怎么了  在我的锁柜里
What'd you do with the diary? It's in my locker
你想让我帮你浏览一边吗?
Hey  do you want me to screen it for you?
划出所有的惊悚的部分
Magic Marker Out all the scary parts
没人在看它
No  No one's reading it
好吧  现在这里不行
Okay  now don't  here
不要太用力  你这是在拉扯皮
Don't pull too hard  You're stretching the skin
阿历克斯抢了我的病人
Alex stole my patient
那人眼睛后面长了一个葡萄
With a grapefruit growing behind his eyes
你的男朋友屁都不放一个
And your boyfriend couldn't give a crap
那种情况下我也不确定
And just in case I wasn't sure
-他其实是说"我屁也不会放一个的"  -看那家伙
He actually said the words  i don't give a crap  Okay  see that guy there  Okay?
他是住院医师
He's a resident
他在煲电话粥  因为他昨天睡太多了
He's dragging 'cause he got too much sleep last night
太多了
Uh-Huh  Too much
什么?
What?
这就像在看现场版的肥皂剧
It's like watching a living freak show
我不讨论性
I don't talk about sex
就当我什么也没说过行不?
Please  let's just pretend I never said even a single word
我从不和任何人讨论性  从不
I don't talk about sex with anyone  ever
-任何性话题  -贝利  我在求你
Not any kind of sex  Bailey  I am begging you
维杰杰
The vah-Jay-Jay
是个未知的国度
Is undiscovered country.
是个女儿国
It is the motherland
你从没到过那
You've never traveled there
你不知道她的风俗和生活习惯
You don't know its customs and ways
就像现在我  一直想去非洲
Now me  I've always wanted to go to africa
但是如果我要去
Uh  but if I go
我需要先学习一些东西
I'm going to have to learn a few things first
我需要做好准备  我需要枪支
I'm going to have to prepare  I'll need shots
带上我的听诊器以防万一
Um  bring my own syringes in case something goes wrong
我还要知道怎么办理签证
And  And I'll want to know how to get to the embassy
好了  你把我搞糊涂了
Just  Okay  now you've lost me
去谈谈吧
Just talk about it
别和我  去和别人说说
Not with me  With the other one
只讨论法则  期望
Just talk about the rules  uh  the expectations
去寻求怎样做到温文尔雅
Figure out how to gracefully demure
如果你不喜欢当地的食物
If you find that you don't like the  The local cuisine
在埃塞俄比亚
In ethiopia
当地人吃煮熟的酸软发馊的面包
They eat stew off of spongy  sour bread
不是每个人都这样
That's not for everyone
梅丽  我需要你
Mer  I need you
嘘  别打扰这气氛
Shh  Harshing the vibe
你们在干什么?
What are you doing?
克里斯蒂娜发现了个神奇的地方
Cristina found this magical world
医生和病人都很开心的地方
Where doctors are happy and patients are pleasant
没有人尖叫和抢手术的地方
And no one is screaming or stealing surgeries
所有人只是相互抚摩
Everyone just rubs each other
-从早到晚  -你们都想做皮肤科医生吗
All day long  You all want to be dermatologists?
皮肤科医生给活人涂抹清洗
Dermatologists apply lotion for a living
这就是关键  坐到这来
Yeah  that's the point  Come here
来这
Come here
他们心无旁骛
They're empty inside
完全没有肉欲
Completely devoid of blood lust
他们不需要对抗任何东西
They don't need to fight for anything
他们不需要给任何人开刀
They don't want to cut anyone open
他们只是喜欢洗涤
They just  love lotion
如果我们只爱洗涤
Do you know how much easier our life would be
你知道我们的生活可以多么简单吗
If we could just love lotion?
你认为他们是怎么做到这些的
How do you think they got that way?
他们的妈妈把自己的日记留着
Their mothers didn't leave diaries around
让他们去拜读
For them to read
斯隆今天告诉我要在荒蛮的西部
Sloan told me today to stake my claim
去争取自己的所有权
In the wild  wild west
我对着爱历克斯的牛仔屁股用尽伎俩
So I went all cowboy on Alex's ass
但是我还是没有拿到我的手术
And I still don't have my surgery
这些女人
These women
她们不需要争取所有权
they do not have to stake a claim
好了 你们都需要想开些
Okay  You all need to snap out of it
伊兹  在蛮荒的西部
Izzie...  in the wild, wild west
总有一个女人在酒吧里
There is always a woman in the saloon
没有人干涉她  虽然他们都带着枪
And nody messes with her  even though they all have guns
她是个妓女
She's a prostitute
在酒吧的女人是个妓女  乔治
The woman in the saloon is a whore  George
不  她只是用了一些其他的伎俩
No  She just has other skills she uses
以自己的方式生活在这个世界上
To make her way in the world
所以你也可以用你的伎俩
So just  uh  use what you got
梅丽  我来拿这个  我需要你
Mer  I'm gonna take this  and I need you
帮我去给汉娜和主任出个主意
To help me sell an idea to Hahn and the chief
克里斯蒂娜
Cristina
你也来
You're coming  too
克里斯蒂娜
Cristina
你怎么样  戈兰蒂先生?
How you doing  Mr  Grandy?
我得了个肿瘤
Well  um  I've got a tumor
就像一个棒球
That's been compared to a baseball
一个外来种的葡萄在我的头里
A grapefruit and an alien living inside my head
我的妻子
And  my wife
要和我离婚
who was ready to divorce me
甚至在她知道我是个病患之前
Even before she knew that I was damaged goods
她甚至不来看我
She won't even look at me
不  我想她只是对肿瘤有点神经过敏
No, I'm sure she's just freaked out about the tumor
-这种情况很多  -如果不是肿瘤会怎样?
It happens a lot. What if it isn't just the tumor?
我的意思是  如果她不知道的话会怎么做
I mean  what if she's figured out
她是不爱我吗?
That she just doesn't like me?
不是的
No
我能肯定  你是个人见人爱的家伙
You're a really likable guy  I can tell
你是个好女孩
You're a nice girl
你的新医生和我一样好吗  克莱夫医生
is your new doctor as nice as me  Dr Karev
他很好
He's all right
好的
That's good
Yeah
他有些个人问题
He was having some personal problems
萎靡不振
Depression
他已经离开工作很久了
He's been a little  off his game  but
离开工作?
Off his game?
这听起来像是他是突然回来的
Well  it sounds like he's bouncing back
没事的  等一会
You'll be fine  Wait a minute
我不想要那些手艺生疏的人
I don't want someone who's off his game
我能让你回来吗
Can I get  uh  you back?
是的  你能去跟谢博德医生谈谈
well  you could talk to Dr Shepherd
告诉他你不想让克莱夫负责你的治疗
Tell him you don't want Dr Karev on your case
然后我就是你的了
And then I'm all yours
-怎么了  -她说她感到无力
What happened? She said she was feeling faint,
我以为她只是在生气
And I thought she was just pissed
-在等她的奶油  -她的脉搏是90
About waiting for her cream  Her pulse ox is 90?
是的  吸氧也没有效果
Yeah  and the oxygen's not helping
送她去急诊室
Get her to the e.R.
-为什么你不送她去急诊室  -我不知道怎么办
-Why didn't you move her to the e.R.? Well  I didn't know what to do
-那你就干站着? -我呼你了! 你自己到底去了哪?
-So you are just standing？-I have paged you, What the hell have you been?
小心点  思德洛斯  给她注射16单位的地塞米松
Supportive care  steroids  Give her 16 of dexamethasone
-来了  -快  快点
-My way  -Hurry  Come on!
血压恢复了
B.P.'S going back up
好了 把贝利医生叫过来
Okay  um  call Dr Bailey
告诉她有个病人要做血浆除去法
And tell her the patient needs a plasmapheresis
和皮肤组织检测
And a skin biopsy stat.
-你抢了我的手术  -那是我的
You stole my surgery. It's my surgery.
其一你把我当成受气包
Using me as a doormat is one thing.
其二你抢走我的工作
Screwing with my career is another.
我已经看透你的无耻了
I have been wiping your snot
把你的屁眼堵一段时间吧
And covering your ass for weeks now,
你做过的一切都是在伤害我
And all you've done is abuse me.
只要一有机会  你就会这么做
And for a little while  you get to do that
因为你心理变态又愚蠢可怜
Because you're heartbroken and pathetic
我们本来是好朋友  但是现在不是了
And I'm a good friend  but it ends now
-去做你自己的手术  收起你的嘴脸  -谢博特医生  那是我的手术
Get your own surgeries and wipe your own snot  Dr Shepherd  that's my surgery
克莱夫  这是病人提出的要求
The patient made the request  Karev
我无能为力
Nothing I can do
她的皮肤60%僵化了  我很惊奇她早上起床的时候
60% of her skin sloughed off  I'm surprised she didn't crash
-没有撞倒什么东西  -斯隆医生来巡视的时候
When she got out of bed this morning  Dr Sloan didn't catch it
没有注意到吗?
When he was down here for a consult?
他可能被我说的话吓到了
Oh  he may have been distracted by the fact
我跟他说那个是皮肤坏死
I told him it was necrotizing fasciitis
的确有这个可能
That would do it
我能做个活组织检查吗
Uh  can I do the biopsy?
哦 好的
Well  sure
我以前不知道你对皮肤学很有兴趣
I didn't know you had a big interest in dermatology.
不  我没兴趣  这只是手术的一部分
No  I don't  just the surgical part
好的  很好  培养其他兴趣
That's all right. It's good. Branch out.
不是的  贝利医生  我对皮肤学没兴趣
No  Dr Bailey  I'm not interested in derm
莫名其妙
atology
我们要做一个皮层切入
We're doing a bicoronal incision
估计会有大量出血
Expect a lot of bleeding
我一切  马上就会出血
Once I get going, it'll all happen fast,
所以跟着我的步骤
So stay with me.
斯蒂文斯  打开电烧灼器
Stevens  grab a bovie
好的  让我们开始
All right  Here we go
你不能带一个8岁的小孩
You are not bringing an 8-Year-Old child
-进手术室  -他很害怕不知道会发生什么
Into the o.R. He's scared and he doesn't know what's gonna happen
-他无法了解这一切  -让那个小男孩去看血腥的手术室
And there is no way for him to imagine it  Letting the boy see a bloody o.R.
不会有任何益处  欧麦利
Isn't gonna help matters  O'malley
汉娜医生一小时后有一个肺切除术
Dr Hahn has a thorascopic lung resection in an hour
-三个很小的创口  没有血  没有恐惧  -这个有什么帮助
Three tiny incisions  no blood  nothing scary  And what's that gonna do?
这会让他了解那个房间  医生还有各种仪器
It's gonna show him the room  the people  the instruments
被麻醉的人依然活着
Someone under anesthesia who's still alive.
扣住他和麻醉他是为了
Pinning him down and doping him up is
帮他做一个外科治疗
it's gonna be traumatic for him and it's
而且这会让他了解这是个很松的扣
showing him how it works is such an easy fix
你看得到吗
You can't see  can you?
看不到
Nope
我不想去那里
I don't want to go in there
不敢了?
Scared?
没事的  没有一丁点血
Well  there's not gonna be any blood
没有什么可怕的东西
Nothing gross  nothing scary
只有三个小口子
It's just three tiny cuts
很小  你几乎看不到它们
That are so small  you can barely see them
我第一次进到那里
The first time that I went in there
进到那个房间  我也不敢
In that room  I was scared
但是那个房间
But that room
是这个世界上最神奇的房间
Is the most magical room in the world
只有最好的医生才能进去
Only the finest doctors get to go in there
他们中有很多都很出色
And a lot of the great ones
但甚至都不被允许碰任何东西
They're not even allowed to touch anything
他们只能看着
They can just watch
我也很优秀  所以我也只能在那里看
I'm pretty good  so I'm still a watcher
能在那里工作的人
The people that work in there, they're just
他们是最棒的  非常非常棒的
They're the best  the very best
那是你在一生中到过的
It's the safest place you'll ever be in
最安全的地方
In your entire life
那个家伙的脸怎么了
Where'd that guy's face go?
你走错了  欧麦利
You lost  O'malley?
对不起
Sorry.
不  等等  让我看  我要看这个没脸的家伙
No, wait! I want to see! I want to see the guy with no face!
停下  放我下来
Stop! Stop!
别跟人提起刚才的事
Never mention this happened to anyone,
我给你看  你毕生都没机会见的东西
I'll give you whatever you want for the rest of your life.
-怎样  -好的
-Okay? -Okay.
下午好  邓肯  欢迎参观
Good afternoon, duncan. Come on in and take a look.
我还是想看刚才那个
I want to go back to the other one.
再也不许提刚才那个
We're not talking about the other one.
这个太无聊了
This one's boring.
是的  我们就是无聊来了
Yeah, we are here be boring, too
会有大灯照着我吗
Do I get the big lights?
是的  所有大灯都会照亮
Yeah, you get all the big lights.
-吸引器在哪  -就在那里
-Where's the suctioner? -It's right over there.
我可以摸一下吗  我只是要感受一下
Can I feel it? I just want to feel it once.
先躺过来
Move over first.
我可以碰解剖刀吗
Can I touch the scalpel?
你只需要躺下就行了
You just need to lie down.
我只是要看看所有的东西
I just want to see everything.
-看这里  看到没  -是的
-Look here. See this? -Yeah.
这是台摄像机
That's a video camera.
手术结束后  你可以看到全过程
You'll be able to watch the whole thing when it's over.
那赶紧开始吧
Start shooting right now.
-怎么了  -躺下
-What?  -Lie down.
手术后见
See you after surgery.
别太用力
Don't squeeze too hard.
镊子上的齿印会留下疤痕的
The teeth on the forceps can leave holes.
这样就行
That's good.
不错  就在这个平面上继续
Very good. Keep going with that plane.
好的  让我看一下
Great. Okay, let me take a look.
牛仔是没有朋友的
Cowboys don't have friends.
格蕾医生  准备好了吗
Dr. Grey, you ready?
看清视角  开始缝合吧
Okay, good visualization, and start suturing right here.
好的  继续
All right. Keep going.
很不错
Very nice.
好了  给她留个小房间  欧麦利
All right. Give her a little room, O'malley.
好的
Okay.
很漂亮
Beautiful.
你可以告诉杨医生
You can tell Dr. Yang
她比我想象中要教得好
She's a better teacher than I would've thought.
对不起
Sorry.
算了吧
Save it.
如果你的同事比你知道得多
If your colleagues know more than you do,
尽可能把别人的知识都挤压到你脑子里
Milk 'em for all they're worth.
但你在经验问题上  还是对我撒了谎
But you lie to me again about your experience,
下次你再想看到心脏
And the next heart you see will be your own
只可能是我用牛排刀  打开的你自己的心脏
As I cut it out of your chest with a steak knife.
戈兰蒂太太
Mrs. Grandy?
你丈夫已开始恢复
your husband is in recovery.
手术难度很大
It was a tough procedure,
但最后  手术还是很成功
But overall, it went really well.
他会好起来的  Grandy太太
He's gonna be okay, Mrs. Grandy.
他再也不会原谅我了
he is never gonna forgive me.
他病了  而我却说他懒惰  无聊
He was sick, and I told him he was lazy and boring.
他生病了  而你并不知道
He was sick. You didn't know.
可我是他太太  我应该知道
Well, I'm his wife. I should've known.
他...
He was...
人们对于自己所爱的人  有时会做出糟糕的事
People are terrible to the people they love sometimes.
有意无意的
They're mean.
你们彼此都在经历一个困难的时期
You were both going through a really hard time,
你恰好表露出来了
And you took it out on one another.
貌似不可思议  但人们的确这么做的
It isn't fun, but it is what people do.
这并不意味着你就是世界上最糟糕的妻子
That doesn't make you the worst wife in the world.
这只说明  你是个会犯错的常人
It just makes you... a person who made a mistake.
我错过什么了吗
I miss anything good?
你会爱死这里的
You're gonna love is.
那个红发的人  把一个病例给了那矮个儿的人
The redhead just gave the short one a case
因为她认为  他会从中获得趣味
Because she thought he'd find it interesting--
我们可以换一下  这样也许我们更加开心
We could transfer  Maybe we'd be happier
我们会无聊而死的
We'd die of boredom
我们整天和皮肤厮混  老死在一起
We'd die with great skin  Hmm
我参加了个个超厉害的皮肤科手术
I had the biggest derm emergency
就在今天
That exists today,
整个过程就1分钟是有意思的
And it was fun for about a minute,
因为一个女人差点死了  但是我们救了她
'Cause a woman almost died, but then we saved her.
-他所需要的只是个傻乎乎的活组织检查  -我把一个家伙的脸切下来了
And all she needed was a stupid biopsy  I tore a guy's face off
我重接了一个冠状动脉
I reattached a coronary artery
我讨厌你们两个
I hate you both
我们不是快乐喜悦的人
We are not happy, glowy people
-是的
Yeah
我们必须离开这
We gotta get outta here
-是的  -是的
Yeah  Yeah
考试还没有结果吗?
Still no word on the test?
-乔治  我确信你通过了  -我没事的
George  I'm sure you passed  It'll be okay
我的意思是  今晚你应该给我买瓶啤酒
I mean  you're gonna buy me a beer tonight  and then
-好的  -那我就会没事了
Oh  right  It's gonna be okay
欧麦利  考试结果
O'malley  Test results
你通过了
You passed
我通过了?
I passed?
乔治  你不再是一个实习生了
George  you're  You're not an intern anymore.
我通过了
I passed
-我们应该好好庆祝下  -我通过了
We are so gonna celebrate  I passed
我通过了
I passed
I pass
我想去告诉伊兹和梅瑞狄斯
I'm gonna  uh  I gotta go tell Izzie and Meredith
去告诉他们  然后我们
No  no  go tell 'em  and  And then we'll
好吧
okay.
干杯  为了乔治·欧麦利不再重考
Huzzah! To George O'malley  repeater no more
你现在无所不能了
You're gonna be impossible now
莱西  来加入我们
Lexie! Come on and join us
我想先喝一杯
Hey  I'm gonna get a drink first
乔  给我来杯啤酒
Hey  joe  Um  could I have a beer?
好的  要帮你送到桌子上去吗
Sure  Want me to bring it to the table?
我要坐到那去
No  uh  I'm  I'm just gonna sit over there
乔  再一杯伏特加
Hey  joe  can I get another vodka tonic?
乔治通过考试了
George passed his exam
走狗
Tool
我在找你
Ah  just the people I was looking for
-乔  我想要两瓶饮料  -你是史上最佳室友
Joe  I want to buy these two a drink. You are the best roommate ever.
我只是被轰走了
I am  Just to be clear
你们两个又可以到我的位置拉屎放屁了
You two ever pull that crap on one of my cases again,
我也不会再让你跟着我了
I will have you thrown out of the program
你知道吗  乔
You know what  joe?
帮我把酒端过来
I'll just take my drink at the table
我知道  我知道我就是个笨蛋
I-I know  okay? I know I'm being an ass
我无能为力
I can't help it.
我总是在发火  我甚至不能呼吸
I'm pissed off all the time, so much, I can't even breathe.
但是你不能对一个疯女人发火
But you can't be pissed at a crazy chick
因为她失去理智了
For losing her mind,
所以除了你没有其他人可以让我发泄
So there's nobody else to be pissed at except you.
没有其他人
Nobody else
我们需要约法三章
We need to have rules
什么?
What?
约法三章  我们需要约法三章
Rules  We--We need rules
我们怎样去处理女儿国的问题
About how we're gonna deal with the motherland.
这是块处女地
Because it's undiscovered country
但是也许
And  maybe
也许这是我们所拥有的
maybe it'll be the best vacation
最棒的旅程
Either of us has ever had,
但是那很隐秘
But  it's mysterious
很黑暗
and dark
需要约法三章
and there should be rules
需要一个制度
oh  and  And an embassy
一个合理的说辞
and a safe word.
不好意思
I'm sorry.
你在说些什么
What the hell are you talking about?
在
Below the
在你裤子的mason-Dixon线
below the mason-Dixon line
的下面
Of your pants
我不确定我准备好了
I'm not sure I'm ready to go there
我也没有
Me neither
在皮带之上
There's lots of undiscovered territory
还有很多未知的领域
above the belt.
我们可以慢慢来
Uh, we can take it slow.
也许...  只是...
Maybe... just...
一垒
first base?
好
Okay.
可以  谢谢你
Whew. Okay. Thank you.
抱歉
Sorry.
来  喝了这杯酒
Here, finish my wine.
我来看看菜单
I'm gonna look at the menu
给你点时间让血压回到正常水平
while you let your blood pressure drop back down to normal.
爱瑞克
Erica.
也许二垒也行
Maybe second base, too.
我还可以搬回车里去
I could always move back to the trailer.
不  我要你呆在这儿
No, I want you here.
我是说我也许有时会发发脾气
I mean, I may not always be so graceful about it,
但我希望你在这儿呆着
But... I want you here.
你需要放东西的空间
You need a place for your things.
这是合理要求
It's not an unreasonable request.
你可以把这个当房间或是办公室什么的
You can use this as your den or your office or whatever.
这是你母亲的房间
It's your mom's den.
她不在这儿
But she isn't here.
你在
You are.
那你呢
What about you?
你也需要空间
You need someplace,
一个能独处的地方
Someplace you can get away to.
我可以去克里斯蒂娜那儿
Well, I can always go to Cristina's or whatever.
我有个更好的主意
I think I have a better idea.
我们希望自己是无惧的
We like to think we're fearless,
渴望开辟新世界  迅速增长经验
eager to explore unknown lands and soak up new experiences,
但事实上  我们永远都会害怕
But the fact is, we're always terrified.
也许恐惧本身就是吸引我们的地方
Maybe the terror is part of the attraction.
有些人选择看恐怖电影
Some people go to horror movies.
我们切开东西  与血液为伴
We cut things open, dive into dark waters.
1977年10月13日
"October 13, 1977.
我连续三天没睡着了
I haven't slept in three days."
到了最后
And at the end of the day,
如果你有一杯酒  一个朋友  以及45分钟时间
isn't that what you'd rather hear about
这难道不是你想听的东西吗
if you've got one drink and one friend and 45 minutes?
平稳的生活很乏味
Smooth rides make for boring stories.
有些患难才是值得交谈的
A little calamity...  That's worth talking about.